<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Altcoin Trading Theme</title>
    <description>Altcoin Trading is the forex of cryptocurrencies, with bitcoin as the base currency.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 13:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 13:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bitcoin ETF rejected, Ethereum ETF is probably off the table too</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/emotions/sadness.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/emotions/sadness.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: Cryptocurrencies are not going to be part of the mainstream finance for now.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today just after 4PM Eastern time the SEC finally dropped the long postponed decision regarding the proposed COIN ETF, the first Bitcoin exchange traded fund.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The SEC cites lack of regulations and the fact that BTC markets can be manipulated as the main reasons for rejection of the rule change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;[…] the Commission is disapproving this proposed rule change because it does not find the proposal to be consistent with Section 6(b)(5) of the Exchange Act, which requires, among other things, that the rules of a national securities exchange be &lt;strong&gt;designed to prevent fraudulent and manipulative acts&lt;/strong&gt; and practices and to protect investors and the public interest. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sec.gov/rules/sro/batsbzx/2017/34-80206.pdf&quot;&gt;Full SEC announcement&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though there is another BTC ETF proposal lined up for the 30th of March and Ethereum has a proposal for listing, it seems that any cryptocurrency exchange traded fund is off the table for now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cryptocoinsnews.com/etherindex-registers-sec-issue-ether-shares/&quot;&gt;EtherIndex, the ETH ETF proposal - 19/07/2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ETC product (created by Barry Silbert’s Grayscale) &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2017-03-09/bitcoin-trust-s-silbert-to-launch-classic-ether-fund-this-month&quot;&gt;is supposed to launch this month though&lt;/a&gt;, even though it will probably start trading over-the-counter first. It is modeled after the Bitcoin Investment Trust (GBTC) which is also a &lt;a href=&quot;https://grayscale.co/bitcoin-investment-trust/&quot;&gt;Grayscale product&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Eventually, just like Bitcoin Investment Trust, it may start trading over the counter, Silbert said in an interview. The bitcoin trust, started in 2013, is currently waiting for approval to list on the NYSE Arca market.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Classic ether’s development and rules governing the nets; recently, developers announced there will be no more than 230 million classic ether tokens issued – a decision that makes the digital currency a scarce resource, just like bitcoin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In short, it is not going to get any easier for legacy investors to trade cryptocurrency in the months to come, but that’s about it. Cryptocurrencies are for now just cryptocurrencies, the niche speculative bet on the future. That’s not quite a reason to panic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;They have two mutually exclusive, and self destructive ideals.
Pursue valuation from regulated sources.
Or undermine those sources they pursue.
These Ideas can’t exist on the same chain, there isn’t some quantum solution. They need to fork to meet both, or continue in purgatory. meanwhile, Ethereum will just find implementation and application as a tool. It really is oil vs gold. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ethtrader/comments/5yoqdr/denied/&quot;&gt;via /r/ethtrader&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/ethereum-etf-unlikely/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/ethereum-etf-unlikely/</guid>
        
        
        <category>coins</category>
        
        <category>eth</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Avoidance Strategy in Altcoin Trading</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/emotions/standby.JPG&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/emotions/standby.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: Wyckoffian Avoidance Strategy?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wyckoff method is getting popular in the cryptocurrency space mainly because John Bollinger the author of bbands keeps recommending it on twitter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While it can be called a “legacy” thing no doubt it is useful for crypto as well:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; data-lang=&quot;en-gb&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/kenzboard&quot;&gt;@kenzboard&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/MrJozza&quot;&gt;@MrJozza&lt;/a&gt; Yeah, Wyckoff is as near to a universal key to understanding trading as we have.&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; John Bollinger (@bbands) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/bbands/status/835170564431962112&quot;&gt;24 February 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-value-trading&quot;&gt;The value trading&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Wyckoff style is to trade only the best stocks in the leading sectors. Can you use this motto when trading cryptocurrencies? It is an emerging asset class but figuring out which cryptocurrency has actual &lt;strong&gt;value&lt;/strong&gt; will make your decisions a lot clearer:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You want to buy/hold a &lt;em&gt;valuable&lt;/em&gt; asset through shorter timespans when the &lt;em&gt;price&lt;/em&gt; is not reflecting the value (yet).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You want to take profits and abandon an asset that is appreciating in the short term because of things like tiny market hence manipulation, or media hype.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;how-strong-a-coin-is&quot;&gt;How strong a coin is&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The Wyckoffian mission is to trade and invest in the best stocks in the leading Industry Groups. We have been studying examples of leadership characteristics using &lt;strong&gt;Wyckoff Analysis&lt;/strong&gt; in combination with &lt;strong&gt;Relative Strength&lt;/strong&gt;. […] Always seeking the strongest stocks in the strongest groups. It is also a worthwhile exercise to study groups that are stalling and falling from favor. &lt;a href=&quot;http://stockcharts.com/articles/wyckoff/2017/02/avoidance-strategy.html&quot;&gt;StockCharts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The key point is that a leader of a group dies not remain a leader indefinitely. At some point the leader leaves the limelight, becomes a laggard and may stay a laggard for some time. That’s what the Wyckoff avoidance strategy is about - spotting the transition from leader to laggard and avoiding longing that market rather than getting to think in forever terms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This transition is a substantial change, technically you should be looking for it on longer timeframes (daily, 3D or weekly charts).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;select-assets-that-are-in-harmony-with-the-market&quot;&gt;Select assets that are in harmony with the market&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;In a &lt;strong&gt;bull (uptrend) market&lt;/strong&gt;, select [assets] that are &lt;strong&gt;stronger than the market itself&lt;/strong&gt;. In a bear market choose those that are weaker than the market itself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you figure out consistently strong cryptocurrencies and their counterparts you have your best candidates for mid-term longs and shorts:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Strong altcoins rally quite easily but after the rally retraces some of the gains remain.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Weak altcoins are traded but don’t rally consistently. If they do, the retrace kills all the gains.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In legacy markets one can compare stocks against a composite index. In a bull market well below a known resistance line, if a stock gains more than the index, it’s typically a good bet to open a long, avoding all the rest of the assets in the group. If the resistance approaches it’s time to close that long and find which stock was performing poorly in the rally. That is going to be to one most likely to drop significantly, you can short it and avoid trading the strong performers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In cryptocurrencies we don’t have an index that would track the performance of top 100 or 500 altcoins. You will have to put in a little bit more work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A handy tool that will help you do that is &lt;a href=&quot;http://coinmarketcap.com/&quot;&gt;coinmarketcap.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can track the historical weekly performance of cryptocurrencies at &lt;a href=&quot;http://coinmarketcap.com/historical/&quot;&gt;http://coinmarketcap.com/historical/&lt;/a&gt; - this page has snapshots dating back to 2013.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Daily data is available at &lt;a href=&quot;http://coinmarketcap.com/#BTC&quot;&gt;the homepage&lt;/a&gt; or from their API. If you are trading altcoins against BTC, that is pairs like ETHBTC, you should switch to BTC pricing. This way you’ll see which altcoins perform the best and the worst against bitcoin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/trading/cmc-snapshot.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/trading/cmc-snapshot.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Going through the weekly data from 2016 you can filter each table by traded volume.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You’ll see that small altcoins show up every week with immense gains but after some weeks you don’t hear about them again.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;On the other hand, for instance litecoin is consistently being traded but the price doesn’t change much - perhaps people use it to move funds across exchanges instead of using fiat but next to no people believe it is worth to hold LTC.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ethereum and Dash have volumes in the upper part of the spectrum but they actually see a rally or two once in a while with gains that don’t completely disappear after the retrace.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;going-back-to-individual-coins&quot;&gt;Going back to individual coins&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To spot the beginning of short term changes in the market, topping patterns and reversals you will have to go back to individual cryptocurrencies. The chart below is a bitcoin chart but the same TA is valid with all commonly traded coins with good holder base these days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What people use the most to spot these changes is Parabolic SAR, RSI and MACD. You can use &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://cryptowat.ch&quot;&gt;Cryptowatch&lt;/a&gt; for the basics or &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://tradingview.go2cloud.org/SHW9&quot;&gt;TradingView&lt;/a&gt; which provides interface where you can tune the indicator parameters and do some very basic backtesting. To name one, the default Parabolic SAR will be too sensitive, giving you flips that will be a false positive so you should pick your timeframe and tune the PSAR settings so that it flips really mostly only before a reversal historically happened on that timeframe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The hourly bitcoin chart below shows a SAR set to &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;0.025, 0.02, 0.03&lt;/code&gt; on &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://tradingview.go2cloud.org/SHW9&quot;&gt;TradingView&lt;/a&gt;. If you click on the picture to zoom it you’ll see it flipping, and if you look at the RSI at the bottom you’ll see a divergence between the RSI lows and the price lows, which is bullish as it shows the lows are too low for the strength of the market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/trading/btc-rsidiv.png&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/trading/btc-rsidiv.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course in both bitcoin and altcoins you cannot discount “conspiracy theories” about whales manipulating the markets - given the (little) money one needs to do that it’s entirely possible. Even the legacy guys found it out themselves, I encourage you to read the following excerpt from FT where an investor whines about getting rekt on OkCoin because of a bearwhale, it’s hilarious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;this is from ft, somehow archive.is works around their log in wall: http://archive.is/aQ7Om&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Daniel Masters, the founder of one of the world’s first bitcoin funds – Jersey-based Global Advisors Bitcoin Investment Program (GABI) – is calling for position limits on bitcoin exchanges, after falling prey to a heinous case of cash-to-futures basis manipulation in February, when bitcoin soared to new record high.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Our position was liquidated at $767 and, needless to say, by the time we were back in the market the price was shooting back above $900. This was of course an extremely unfortunate state of affairs in which to find ourselves and a hard lesson learned. Accordingly, we lost around 10% of performance against our benchmark, the USD price of bitcoin. The matters set out above highlighted another issue with bitcoin trading, which up until this point we had not considered. After the price drop, one player emerged as totally dominant in the open interest of the futures contract. It seemed pretty clear to us as a result that this event was not just a normal version of a large liquidation, with which we are familiar, but was a premeditated attack. When the dust settled, one unidentified player was short well over half the open interest. We would therefore class this episode as clear market manipulation, and in fact it was not just momentary: for many days thereafter the basis was so weak that it seemed that the one attack was being followed up by periodic smaller attacks. As such we approached the exchange. They confirmed to us that there were no position limits whatsoever and that people were free to do whatever they wanted in their “happy trading environment” (yes, they used those actual words). We made it very clear that such activity, whether in a regulated environment or not, might amount to criminality in Hong Kong and would certainly do so in many other jurisdictions. Following a number of discussions, the exchange encouraged the ‘rogue’ player to withdraw and things have now normalized.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“happy trading environment” from hong kong…that’s okcasino amirite &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/BitcoinMarkets/comments/5y5qzz/daily_discussion_wednesday_march_08_2017/deo070z/&quot;&gt;via r/bitcoinmarkets&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the next days I’ll be looking over altcoins historical performance so stay tuned for next posts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reading&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://technical.traders.com/tradersonline/display.asp?art=167&quot;&gt;http://technical.traders.com/tradersonline/display.asp?art=167&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://stockcharts.com/articles/wyckoff/&quot;&gt;https://stockcharts.com/articles/wyckoff/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/wyckoff-avoidance/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/wyckoff-avoidance/</guid>
        
        
        <category>trading</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Back to Basics: How to buy altcoins</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/img/eth/eth2.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;border&quot;&gt;&lt;amp-img itemprop=&quot;image&quot; src=&quot;/img/eth/eth2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; layout=&quot;responsive&quot; width=&quot;700px&quot; height=&quot;360px&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: Ethereum, Monero and the rest of it: How to buy?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;buying-bitcoin-first&quot;&gt;Buying bitcoin first&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Getting an altcoin for your bitcoins that you already bought on &lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://localbitcoins.com/?ch=4nq3&quot;&gt;localbitcoins&lt;/a&gt; or elsewhere is the classic way to start holding or trading altcoins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These days, after 27 Jan 2017, it is vital to check if you’re getting clean coins though. &lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcointalk.org/index.php?topic=1766723.0&quot;&gt;Yesterday someone published a list of transactions&lt;/a&gt; that proved the bitcoins stolen in the Bitfinex hack in august 2016 started moving. Apparently the hacker is now trying to move small chunks of the coins to bitcoin exchanges. It is likely that they might try to use a mixing service to clean the bitcoin or that they will even set up their own mixer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Therefore always check where did your bitcoins came from - even if you just deposited them for lending on Poloniex. You will probably not be getting back your original bitcoins but bitcoins with a different history.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Buy and hold&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you just want to buy an altcoin like Monero, Ether, Dash, Factom or Maid, you can use ShapeShift. You don’t need a user account, you simply send in the money. You need to have bitcoins or an altcoin and a wallet address where you want to receive the altcoin you’re buying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://shapeshift.io/#/coins&quot;&gt;ShapeShift&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trading Alt/BTC pairs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Mecca of altcoin trading. Poloniex usually lists new coins reasonably fast, all the intial trading of a new coin usually happens there. You can buy and sell on spot, you can long and short with margin and you can lend out any coin for interest. The web app is kind of sluggish at times but API is reliable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://poloniex.com&quot;&gt;Poloniex&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some smaller altcoins are not listed on Polo though. In such case they will probably be on Bittrex.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://bittrex.com/home/markets&quot;&gt;Bittrex&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Try and avoid Hitbtc, they don’t have a good reputation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;getting-altcoins-for-fiat&quot;&gt;Getting altcoins for fiat&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kraken&lt;/strong&gt; / US (SEPA, wire)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Altcoins: Ether, Ether Classic, Iconomi, Litecoin, Augur, Dogecoin, Lumen, Monero, Ripple, Zcash&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.kraken.com/en-gb/help/fees&quot;&gt;Kraken fee structure coin by coin&lt;/a&gt; shows the rates for buying an altcoin with cash might be easily the lowest for you. You need to get verified though and the support is kind of slow. And in addition to that, on slower days the less popular markets are pretty much abandoned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bitfinex&lt;/strong&gt; / HK (wire only)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Altcoins: Ether, Ether Classic, Zcash, Monero, DASH, Litecoin&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.bitfinex.com/?refcode=5egV78YtlC&quot;&gt;Get 10% off fees on Bitfinex&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is not cheap to get money to Bitfinex but their trading interface has no competition. If you want to margin  trade one of the coins that are listed on Bitfinex, go for it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Coincheck&lt;/strong&gt; / JP (wire or debit card - overseas cards limited to 10.000 yen a day)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Altcoins: Ether, Ether Classic, Lisk, Factom, Monero, Augur, Ripple, Zcash&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://coincheck.com/?c=IHffq2cUTu4&quot;&gt;Coincheck has a zero-fee campaign through Feb and Mar 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Coincheck is one of the Japanese exchanges that are now getting the speculators who used to be trading bitcoin in China for as long as there was the zero-fee policy. Coincheck is one of the smaller exchanges. &lt;a href=&quot;https://bitflyer.jp/discussion/roger-ver?top_link&amp;amp;footer&quot;&gt;Bitflyer&lt;/a&gt; seems to be the one that profits from the Chinese ban on zerofee trading but Coincheck is the one that has a fine selection of altcoins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BTC-e&lt;/strong&gt; / RU (SEPA, eWallets, wire)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Altcoins: Litecoin, Dash, Peercoin, Namecoin, Novacoin, Ether&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://btc-e.com/page/2&quot;&gt;Trading fee is always 0.2 perc&lt;/a&gt; and prices are lower but deposit and withdrawal fees make up for it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BitStamp&lt;/strong&gt; / EU (SEPA, wire)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Altcoins: Ripple&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;external&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.bitstamp.net/market/tradeview/&quot;&gt;Bitstamp’s tradeview&lt;/a&gt; is good but liquidity is next to nonexistent. When they setup a new market, like just now with Ripple, nobody is really running in to trade there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;altcoin-storage-the-altcoin-wallets&quot;&gt;Altcoin Storage: The Altcoin Wallets&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have two options - an altcoin-specific wallet or a multi-altcoin wallet. In any case, it is always a bad idea to leave your coin on an exchange. That doesn’t mean that an altcoin in an altcoin-specific wallet is automatically 100% safe though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Keep in mind that all altcoins are works in progress - even the big ones like Ether. &lt;strong&gt;There are bugs in the software&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/ethereum/mist/releases&quot;&gt;See the Ethereum’s Mist release notes on Github&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because of that, proprietary wallets might not always be the best bet. The Jaxx might be much better - but it doesn’t support all the altcoins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will need to compromise a bit but it certainly won’t hurt if you simulate cold storage by having your desktop wallets on a computer that is mostly offline and that you don’t use for your day to day web browsing or downloading.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/altcoin-wallets/&quot;&gt;Full post on altcoin wallets here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-to-buy-altcoins/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-to-buy-altcoins/</guid>
        
        <category>popular</category>
        
        
        <category>exchanges</category>
        
        <category>dash</category>
        
        <category>zcash</category>
        
        <category>eth</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
